This building was originally a 14th-century castle.
♬ 静寂の底から
It was converted into a hotel in the early 1900s.
Ten years ago, it was closed after its owner suddenly died.
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
Now it's been turned into a shelter from the sun by Cars.
♬ 深紅の血潮が
The enemy lurks within, but Jojo and Lisa Lisa know nothing of the hotel's layout!
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 21: "One Hundred Versus Two"
Damn it!
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)ちくしょう！ 何だ
この薄気味悪い クモの巣は！
What's with the creepy cobwebs?
This place needs cleaning!
掃除ぐらい しやがれ！
そうでなくても➡
It's already depressing enough without these decorations!
こちとら 目いっぱい
落ち込みムードなのによ！
But just look at this trail of blood...
しかし この点々と続く出血量！
ワムウは 相当の
波紋ダメージを食らっているな｡
Wham took a heavy beating from the Ripple.
Caesar didn't go down without a fight.
やはり シーザーのやつは
ただでは やられなかった｡
(手刀の音)
We can't let him recover from this!
やつに 回復の時間は与えないぜ！
奥へ進むぜ リサリサ先生！
We're going in, Master Lisa Lisa!
ぎゃ！
(ﾘｻﾘｻ)どうしたの？
What is it?
W-Well...
い… いや｡
T-This doorknob feels really strange...
え… えらく気持ち悪いぜ！
このドアノブは｡
It felt like I was grabbing some guy's hand.
ごついおっさんの手を
握ってるみてえに 気色悪いぜ｡
≪(ﾍﾞｯｸ)ドアじゃねえズラ｡
何？
I'm not a door, man!
Huh?!
What are you looking for, man? I said I'm not a door, man!
≪(ﾍﾞｯｸ)どこ見てるズラ！
ドアじゃあねえって言ったズラ！
あっ！
(ﾍﾞｯｸ)WRRRRYYYYYYY！
でっ きゅっ…｡
吸血鬼！
A vampire!
危ない ジョジョ！
Look out, Jojo!
(ﾍﾞｯｸ)キャアッ！
うあっ！
ジョジョ！
Jojo!
(ﾍﾞｯｸ)CHHEYYY！➡
If it weren't for that weapon, I'd have peeled your face right off!
その武器さえなければ
顔の皮を マスクを剥ぐように➡
そぎ取ってやったものを！
ヘヘヘヘッ
俺の名は ｢鋼鉄のベック｣ズラ｡➡
The name's Wired Beck, man.
I killed my lover and escaped from prison.
もともと 恋人を絞め殺した
脱獄囚だったけど➡
But then Lord Cars made me part of his gang with a mask, man.
逃亡中 カーズ様が 石仮面で
俺を仲間にしてくれたズラ｡
忠誠を感じてるズラ｡
He has my loyalty, man.
お前らごときを
この奥で お休み中の➡
I'm not gonna to let you waltz in and disturb Lord Cars' rest, man.
カーズ様たちの所へは
行かせないズラ｡
やつら！ ついに➡
Those fiends! So they're already unleashing their hounds on people?!
人間界に てめえらの食料を
広め始めたのか！
HNHNHNNHNHNNN～｡
Gimme a break.
やれやれだぜ｡
You're just a pawn damned for Hell.
てめえは きちっと死んで
地獄へ行くべきクズ！
Here, let me give you a little push into the abyss!
どれ！ この俺が
地獄の穴へ 背中を押してやるぜ！
あっ？ リサリサ？
Lisa Lisa?
HMNNN｡
Beautiful, man! Magnificent, man! Your skin's so smooth, man!
美人だズラ｡ まぶいズラ｡
きれいな肌してるズラ｡
抱き締めて その白い肌から
血を吸ってやるズラ！
Come here! Let me drink your life through that skin, man!
私は 今 機嫌が悪い｡
I'm in a bad mood.
お前のような 下品者とは
口も利きたくないし➡
I don't want to hear or see a thing from a lowlife like you.
顔も見たくない｡
But if you want to grab me, just try.
でも 抱き締めるというなら
試してみなさい｡
It will be the last thing you ever do.
後悔しながら死んでもいいならね｡
WOOFHOFHOOO！
Spikes!
針！
こ… これだったのか！
So that's what those are!
10本に見えたのは 指じゃねえ！
針だ！
They're not fingers, they're spikes!
体毛が変化したらしい剛針線が
全身から 飛び出した！
He's covered in wire-like body hair!
I don't like it when women joke at my expense, man.
俺は 女が俺に対して
冗談を言うのは 好まねえズラ｡
そういう場合は お仕置きだズラ｡
Girls who laugh at me get punished, man!
ぎゅ～っと抱き締める！
抱き締めの お仕置きズラ！
I'll give you a little squeeze!
I'll hug you to death, man!
Yikes! He's faster than I thought!
ヤバい！
予想以上に やつは素早い！
Her scarf!
マフラー!? なるほど｡
I see. Lisa Lisa's scarf becomes a Ripple-infused weapon!
リサリサは マフラーに
波紋を通して 武器にするのか！
んん？
What's with the scarf?
何？ このマフラー｡
HYAHAAA！
俺を縛ったつもり？
You wanna catch me?
Don't make me laugh, man!
笑っちゃうズラ！
へ～ん こんなも～んズラ｡
And now I'm free, man!
Uh... What?
っと！ あれ？
どこに行くんだズラ!?
Where are you going, man?
Come, Jojo. Let's move.
さあ ジョジョ 奥へ行くわよ｡
Uh, okay.
あ… ああ｡ ん～！
リサリサの動き
まさに シルクのような滑らかさ｡
Lisa Lisa's movements flow like silk...
She doesn't waste any effort!
それでいて
一分の無駄もなかった！
Hey, quit ignoring me, man!
こら！ 無視すんなズラ！
Hey, you!
おい！ お前｡
ああいう女は やっぱり➡
A woman like that deserves to be punished, right?
徹底的な お仕置きしかないと
思うだろ？
Oh no, man. Your time is up, man.
オーノーだズラ｡
お前 もう 駄目ズラ｡
逆に お仕置きされちまったズラ｡
You're the one who's getting punished, man.
You got a dose of the Ripple, man.
波紋を流されてしまったズラ｡
はぁ？
ヘヘヘ！
バカ言うんじゃねえズ…｡
Don't be ridiculous, ma-
ラッ！
OHHHHH NOOOOOO！
She really is as strong as I thought!
こいつは 頼りになるぜ！
女だから 戦いには向いてねえと
思っていたが➡
I thought she'd be weak in a fight, but she's better than me!
動きが 俺のような素人じゃねえ！
I'm impressed!
びっくりしたぜ！
さすが 波紋の先生だ！
As expected from my Ripple master!
ところで ジョジョ｡
By the way, Jojo...
You still haven't taken the antidote Caesar won for you, have you?
あなた
シーザーが奪ってくれた解毒剤➡
まだ 飲んでないわね｡
あ？ ああ これか？
This?
なぜ？
Why?
I'll drink it after I beat Wham.
ワムウを倒してから
飲むことにしたぜ｡
ヘヘヘッ｡
このピアスは もう既に➡
This ring isn't just a promise between Wham and I anymore.
ワムウとの間にできた約束
じゃあなくなった｡
この戦いに勝って
生き延びるという➡
Now it represent a promise to Caesar to fight and keep living.
シーザーとの約束に変わったのさ｡
リサリサ あんたが そのときまで
代わりに持っててくれねえかい？
Lisa Lisa, will you hold onto it for me until I need it?
いいえ｡
No.
You should keep it.
それは
あなたが持っているべきよ｡
There's no telling what might happen to me.
私にも
何があるか分からないもの｡
えっ？
As they went deeper, Wham's trail of blood grew even thinner.
〈奥へ奥へと続く
ワムウの血の間隔は➡
しだいしだいに 広くなっていた｡
それが 何を意味するのか…➡
Jojo and Lisa Lisa were fully aware what this meant...
ジョジョと リサリサには
十分 分かっていた｡➡
Wham's wounds were healing!
ワムウの傷は
回復しつつあるのだ！〉
They're here.
(ﾜﾑｳ)来たか…｡
待っていたぞ｡
I've been waiting.
You've grown quite a lot.
成長したらしいな｡ 実に！
Bastard, you killed Caesar!
てめえ！
この野郎が シーザーを！
落ち着いて ジョジョ｡
ワムウより 床を見るのよ｡
Look at the floor, Jojo. You need to forget about Wham for now.
Don't worry. My head is cool.
心配ねえぜ｡ 俺の頭はクールだぜ｡
I noticed it, too. The footprints, right?
気付いているよ｡
床の足跡のことだろう？
There are two sets.
もう１人分ある｡
That means Cars is here! Where is he?!
つまり カーズのだ！
どこに隠れているんだ!?
てめえも 姿を見せやがれ！
Quit hiding and show your face!
そう ２人分の足跡しかない｡
Yes, two sets of footprints.
この部屋には
呼吸の気配は 何十とあるのに！
Even though I feel the breathing lungs
of dozens of people in this room!
えっ!?
It's her. I see...
(ﾜﾑｳ)こいつか…｡
なるほど｡ 女にして
この冷静なる判断力！ 洞察力！
You're quite composed and perceptive for a woman.
I can see how Jojo and Caesar learned so much in such a short time.
ジョジョとシーザーを 短期間に➡
あれほどの戦士として
育てられるわけだ！
And you're even capable of feeling such slight breathing.
(ﾜﾑｳ)それに この微妙な
呼吸の気配を感じるとは➡
You're among the finest of the Ripple warriors.
波紋戦士としても 超一流と見た！
W... What the-?!
な… 何だ!?
Y-You guys, you're all vampires, aren't you? Dammit!
て… てめえら！
全員 吸血鬼か ちくしょう！
No response? How creepy!
無反応!? 何たる不気味だ！
カーズ！
Cars!
(指を鳴らす音)
(吸血鬼１)既に我々は
カーズ様に 永遠の命を授かった➡
Lord Cars gave us, his chosen few, eternal life!
選ばれたる者｡ そう 100対２よ！
It's one-hundred against two!
号令と同時に
俺たちが 貴様ら２人を➡
When our master gives the order,
we'll tear you both to shreds, Jojo!
こま切れに 引き裂いてやるぜ！
ジョジョ！
(吸血鬼たち)
オオオオオオ オオオオオオン！
うう！
う… う…｡
ん…
こ… こりゃあ駄目だ！ 100対２！
T-This is bad. One-hundred on two...
Lisa Lisa, we can't win this one!
リサリサ～ もう勝てっこねえ！
Wait, Lord Cars!
(ﾜﾑｳ)お待ちを！ カーズ様！
この男と私は
ローマで 決闘の約束をしました｡
Back in Rome, we promised to fight each other.
エシディシ様が倒れた
遺恨もあります｡
I want to avenge Master AC/DC.
ぜひ 戦いの許可を！
Please allow me to fight.
I shall not.
ならぬ！ 我々の目的は➡
Our goal is to obtain the Red Stone of Aja.
あくまで エイジャの赤石を
手に入れること｡➡
Never forget that, Wham.
忘れるな！ ワムウ｡
はっ！
Right...
That's right! There's no way! I don't even feel like it anymore.
そう！ 駄目 駄目！
俺も もう やる気しねえぜ｡
I'm pretty sure I could beat you anyway.
お前に勝つ自信は あるぜ｡
でもよ お前に勝ってもよ！
But even if I did, I've still got all these vampires hanging out...
こんなに
吸血鬼がいるんじゃあな｡
Win or lose, it's lights out for me, right?
勝っても 負けても
どっちみち死ぬんじゃあな～｡
With those odds, giving up is the only rational choice.
圧倒的不利になると
もう ふてくされるしかないね｡
I'm throwing in the towel.
もう 投～げた！
でっ！
ちくしょう！ 丸見えだったのね｡
Shit! Did you all just see that?
糸の結界で 波紋 流して
一気に やっつけようと思ったが｡
And here I thought I could zap them all at once.
Right, kill the both of them!
よし ２人を殺せ！
If you kill us, you'll never have the Red Stone.
私たちを殺したら
赤石は 永遠に手に入らないわよ｡
Hold it!
待て！ 何だと？ 女｡
What was that, woman?
I'm not so naive that I would bring the Red Stone here with me.
ここへ 赤石を持って
やってくるほど➡
私は まぬけではないわ｡
ある所 ある時刻➡
If neither I nor Jojo are at a certain location at a specific time...
私か ジョジョが
そこへ戻らなければ➡
赤石は 時限装置で爆破されるわ！
...the Red Stone will be destroyed by a time bomb!
フフッ｡ 女 ハッタリはやめろ｡
Woman, don't try this with me.
あなたたちに その時刻までに➡
Are you that confident that you'll be able to find it in time?
その場所を
突き止められるかしら？
The bomb itself is tiny,
but more than enough to destroy the Red Stone.
爆発は ほんの小さなものよ｡
でも 赤石に傷を付けるには 十分｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ぬうう｡
Is there really a time bomb? She never mentioned this...
《時限爆弾て ホントかな？➡
俺は 知らねえけど でも
ここは お調子者でいこう！》
I'll just run with it!
Yeah, it's all true!
うんうん そのとおり！
If we die, it goes boom! Kaboom!
俺たちが死んだら BOMBよ BOMB！
Even so, we can't let you out of here alive.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)だからといって このまま
生きて帰すわけにはいかぬ！
そこで 提案があるわ！
I have a suggestion.
Jojo and Wham can fight one-on-one.
ジョジョとワムウが
１対１で 決闘をする！
And myself and Cars will also fight one-on-one.
私とカーズ
あなたが １対１で戦う！
And to the winner... goes the Red Stone!
その戦いに 私は 赤石を懸ける！
げっ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)何!?
What?!
The victor will win the Stone and their future.
どっちみち 勝者が
赤石と未来を手にするのだわ｡
It will all be clear.
これで すっきりするわ！
Who will hold the Red Stone, you or us?
赤石を手にするのが
あなたたちか 私たちか｡
Who will survive? The Pillar Men or humankind?
生き残るのが
柱の闇の一族か 私たち人間か！
Damn woman!
この女！
(ﾜﾑｳ)フフッ｡
Wham!
ワムウ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)はっ！
It's laughable, Lord Cars.
失笑でした カーズ様｡
S-She's good!
《う… うまいぜ！ リサリサ➡
Lisa Lisa... She's a far better gambler than I could ever dream to be.
この人 俺なんか
及びもしねえほど➡
駆け引きが
うめえんじゃねえの!?》
フフッ｡ 女 いい度胸だ｡
Woman, you have gumption.
いいだろう｡
赤石のために受けてやる！
Very well! We will fight for the Red Stone.
Just don't delude yourselves!
だが うぬぼれるな！➡
貴様らに 明日はない！
You have no tomorrow!
She just turned our luck around to give us more-or-less even odds!
《圧倒的 形勢不利が➡
一気に 対等のところまで
持ち込んだぜ！ この人》
All right, then. Let's do it!
こうなったら やってやるぜ！
(吸血鬼たち)フヘヘヘ…｡
We need a proper time and place for our battle.
決闘には それにふさわしい
時と場所が必要だな｡
ワムウ 希望を言え｡
Wham, your thoughts?
(ﾜﾑｳ)今夜は満月！
時はそれ！ 場所は…｡
We fight tonight, under the full moon!
The place will be at the foot of Mt. Piz Berlina,
fifteen kilometers southeast of here.
ここから 南東へ15kmの
ピッツベルリナ山 山麓｡
｢骸骨の踵石｣と呼ばれる
古代サークルストーン｡➡
We shall meet at the ancient stone circle
named Skeleton Heel Stone.
多くの戦士たちが 光栄と
死の運命を分け合った所だ！
Many warriors have found either death or glory in that place.
サークルストーン？
A stone circle?
こら！ 勝手に決めんなよ！
てめえらに有利な条件を！
Hey, you can't just pick a place that suits your fancy!
ワムウ！ なかなか面白い選択だ！
Wham, that's an interesting choice.
そして ところで 赤石だ…
ジョジョ！➡
Now, about the Red Stone...
Jojo!
Bring the Red Stone to the stone circle at midnight tonight.
貴様が 今夜 真夜中の12時➡
赤石を
サークルストーンまで持ってこい｡
And be sure that bomb is removed.
時限装置とやらを外してな｡
The woman stays here as insurance!
女は人質として ここへ残る！
♬～
リサリサ！
Lisa Lisa!
They don't want us to run.
私たちが このまま
逃げないようにする…｡
当然の要求だわ｡
ジョジョ 赤石を取ってくるのよ｡
It's a reasonable request. Jojo, go and fetch the Red Stone.
Don't worry about me.
私は 心配ないわ｡
ああ｡ 必ず 決闘場へ行くぜ！
信用してくれ｡
Right. I'll see you at the arena.
Trust me.
分かってるわ｡
I do.
Caesar...
シーザー…｡
くっ！
何か俺… 昨日までは
自分のことだけ考えて生きてきた｡
Until yesterday, I lived only thinking of myself.
でも 今 メラメラと
湧き上ってくる この気持ちは…｡
But there's a new feeling burning inside me now...
Is this compassion?
これが ｢仁｣てものか｡
Damn it! I just want to wreck those bastards!
ちくしょう！ あの野郎どもを➡
ぶっ倒したくてしょうがねえぜ！
このジョジョは！
I'll do it for Caesar, Messina, Lisa Lisa and for everyone else!
シーザーや このメッシーナ
リサリサ みんなの思いのために｡
I'll fight for all of you!
戦ってやるぜ！
ヘヘヘ｡ やっぱり 時限爆弾なんて
仕掛けてなかったぜ｡
As I thought, there's no bomb at all.
リサリサ あんな状態で
ハッタリとは 大したタマだぜ｡
Lisa Lisa, you're deceptive, even under pressure!
Now, maybe I should bring you a change of panties, hmm?
ど～れ ついでに➡
パンティの着替えでも
持ってってやるかな ゲヘヘッ｡
Whyat are these photos?
ニャンだ？ この写真は｡
It's Granny Erina!
エリナおばあちゃん
じゃあねえか！
Why would Lisa Lisa have this?
何で リサリサが こんな写真を…
ん？
何だ？ こっちの写真は｡
Who are these people?
｢1889年５月｣？
May 1889?
It's fifty years old!
50年前のだ！
この若い男は スピードワゴン！
This young man is Speedwagon!
エリナおばあちゃん｡
Granny Erina!
And Straits is holding a baby!
そして ストレイツォが
赤ん坊を抱いている！
Lisa Lisa... That's right,
I really know nothing about her life or her past!
リサリサ… そういや 俺は➡
あの女の私生活や 過去を
何にも知らねえ！
一体 この写真を なぜ彼女が!?
Why does she have these photos?
♬～
フッ｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)よし 本物だ｡
我々も 約束を守ろう｡
It's the real thing.
We accept your bargain.
We'll fight you one-on-one!
１対１の決闘を行ってやる！
あっ…｡
この写真を見たということは
話さなくてはならないようね｡
Now that you've seen these photos,
I guess I owe you an explanation.
Actually, I had planned to tell you before the fight.
いや 戦いの前に
話そうと思っていたわ｡
あんた 何者だ？
Just who are you?
50年前…｡
Fifty years ago...
エリナさんは 大西洋の船の上で
夫 ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ･ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰを失った｡
Erina lost her husband, Jonathan Joestar, on a ship sailing the Pacific.
He was your grandfather.
つまり あなたのおじいさんを｡
エリナさんは そのとき
１人の女の赤ちゃんの命を救った｡
That day, your grandmother Erina saved a baby girl's life.
That was me.
それが 私｡
その写真の赤ちゃんは 私｡
The baby in that picture is me.
ち… ちょっと待て！ 50年前だぜ｡
H-Hang on now.
That was fifty years ago!
If you were a baby fifty years ago...
50年前に 赤ん坊ってことは…｡
お… お前
一体 年 いくつなんだ!?
H-Hey! How old are you, anyway?!
ご… 50歳!?
Y-You're fifty?!
I... I... If you're fifty, that means you're a...
おっ おっ おっ おっ お前！
50歳といやあ つまり…
ば… ばばあ！
...g-g-gran-!
だよん｡ 普通｡
Right? Normally...
Y-You look like you're in your late 20s...
ど… どう見ても 20代後半…｡
They say Ripple energy is full of life and keeps you young...
波紋は 生命のエネルギー
若々しさを保つというが…｡
But I guess this is why you don't behave like a young woman at all.
でも道理で！ 態度や物腰は➡
全然
キャワユくないと思ったけど｡
Ah, I think I see a wrinkle behind those shades!
あっ！ サングラスの隙間に
小じわ見っけ！
Just kidding!
とか言ったりして｡
Now, prepare the arena!
よし 闘技場の用意をしろ！
火を放て！
Light the fires!
(吸血鬼たち)ウォォォーン！
ゆっくり話しても
いられないようだけど｡
There's no time to talk now.
It will wait until later.
しかし 話さなくてはならない｡
You and I share common roots.
私のルーツは
あなたにも 関係あるのだから｡
Roots?
ルーツ？
石仮面のため 両親を失い➡
The stone mask killed my parents.
Since Erina was pregnant when she rescued me...
エリナさんに命を救われた
赤ん坊の私は➡
エリナさんが みごもっていたため
ストレイツォに育てられました｡
...I was raised by Straits.
A-Are you serious? By Straits?
な… 何だって！ ストレイツォ！
波紋を身に付けたのも
ストレイツォから｡
Straits taught me about the Ripple.
赤石を受け継いだのも
ストレイツォから｡
Straits gave me the Red Stone.
S-So... Straits is your foster father!
つまり ス… ストレイツォは
あんたの育ての親ってことか！
ストレイツォが 老いを気にして➡
It's tragic that the fear of aging drove Straits to such madness.
あのような狂気に走ったのは
残念でなりません｡
ジョジョ あなたが
あの人を倒したというのは➡
Jojo, my feelings about you killing him are complicated...
複雑な気持ちがしますけど…｡
しかたのない
運命だったのでしょう｡
...but it feels like it was destiny.
What can I say?
《なんてこった！
ホ… ホントに 複雑な気分だぜ｡➡
I-It really is complicated.
なんて 奇妙な人間関係なんだ｡➡
What a bizarre relationship!
Lisa Lisa carries a past full of sadness...
リサリサ この人も
悲しい人生を背負っていた》
(地鳴り)
ジョジョ 話は おしまいのようよ｡
Jojo, we're out of time.
な… 何だ？ この地響きは！
W-What's that rumbling?
(吸血鬼たち)オォッ オォー！
来たな！ こいつがそろえば
いよいよ 決闘が始まる｡
They're here. Now the battle can begin.
(吸血鬼たち)うお～！
こ… これは!?
T-They're-!
(吸血鬼たち)ギャアアアア！➡
ぐあっ ぐあっ！
Outta the way! I could give a damn if I crush ya!
(御者吸血鬼１)どけどけ！
踏み潰されても知らぬぞ！
I-Is that a d-dinosaur?!
な… 何だ!? この き… 恐竜は｡
N-No, horse! It's a horse!
い… いや馬!? 馬か！
Lord Cars, Lord Wham, please move!
(御者吸血鬼２)
カーズ様 ワムウ様！ おどきを！
They've gone mad!
殺気立って
私の手には負えません！
Lord Wham, please!
(御者吸血鬼２)
ワムウ様 おどきを！
(ﾜﾑｳ)むん｡
うむ｡ いい戦車馬だ｡
What fine steeds.
We used masks to turn these horses into vampires.
この馬の脳には
骨針が打ち込んであり➡
吸血馬としてある｡
きゅ… 吸血馬だと？
V-Vampire horses?!
今より この闘技場で
ワムウ対ジョジョの➡
In this arena, Jojo will face Wham in an ancient-style chariot duel!
古式にのっとった戦車戦を
実施する！
(吸血鬼たち)うお～！
A chariot duel?!
戦車戦!?
A true ancient Roman death match!
(御者吸血鬼１)
古代ﾛｰﾏの戦車ﾃﾞｽﾏｯﾁ｡
この戦車に乗り
闘技場を➡
You'll ride through the arena while you fight!
戦いながら
走り続ける！
Lord Wham or Jojo? Who will fall or be beaten down while riding?
ワムウ様か ジョジョ！
どちらかが
振り落とされるか➡
あるいは 走りの途中で
たたきのめされるか！
ゴールは 死のみ！
Defeat means death!
やってもらうぞ
ジョジョ！
That's the rules, Jojo!
この吸血馬は
150馬力！➡
These beasts have the power of 150 horses!
Even Lord Wham has difficulty controlling them.
ワムウ様にとっても
操るのは 骨が折れる｡
こら！ 待ちな！
Hey, wait a minute!
I'll fight you wherever the hell you want...
戦車戦だろうが
何だろうが受けてやる｡
しかし 吸血馬だと!?
...but vampire horses are your minions, right?!
てめえらの
手下じゃあねえか！
Worry not. The reins conduct the Ripple.
(ｶｰｽﾞ)心配するな｡➡
手綱は 波紋が通るように
できている｡
ワムウは パワーで馬を操るが➡
Wham will use his strength.
You can use the Ripple to control them.
お前は 吸血馬を
波紋で操ることができる｡
S-Seriously? They look pretty vicious!
ホ… ホントか!?
凶暴だぜ！
危ねえ！ おい！
Watch out! Hey!
(吸血馬の鳴き声)
I see. Even a little Ripple does it.
なるほど｡
軽い波紋で 操れるわ｡
(吸血鬼たち)
ワムウ！ ワムウ！➡
Wham! Wham! Wham! Wham!
ワムウ！
ワムウ！ ワムウ！➡
ワムウ！ ワムウ！
(吸血鬼たち)うお～！
Wham chose an ancient form for this battle.
ワムウ…➡
古式にのっとった
戦いの装束｡
He must be serious about this.
ワムウのやつ 本気だな｡
決して 今
やつは この戦いを➡
He's not doing this for fun, or even trying to make a sport of it.
楽しんでいたり
甘く見たりしてはいない｡
勝ちなさい ジョジョ！
我々は 勝たなくてはならない｡
Beat him, Jojo. We have to win this.
引き分けはない！
There are no draws!
Wham!
ワムウ！
I haven't taken this antidote yet!
まだ この解毒剤は
飲んじゃあいねえぜ！
てめえを ぶっ殺してからという➡
I promised Caesar I'd drink it after I killed you!
シーザーと俺の誓いになったんだ｡
この誓いは 俺に 今まで以上の
パワーを与えてくれるだろう｡
That promise will give me power I've never seen before!
一緒に戦ってくれ シーザー！
Fight alongside me, Caesar!
いくぜ！ 戦車戦！
Lets start this chariot duel!
(吸血馬の鳴き声)
Along the drifting cloud, the eagle searching down on the land
Catching the swirling wind, the sailor sees the rim of the land
The eagle's dancing wings create, as weather spins out of hand
(吸血鬼たち)
ワムウ！ ワムウ！ ワムウ！➡
ワムウ！ ワムウ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)スタート！
Go closer hold the land, feel partly no more than grains of sand
We stand to lose all time, a thousand answers by in our hand
Next to your deeper fears, we stand surrounded by million years
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out and out
Next Episode
Wham! Wham! Wham! Wham!
Start!
Episode 22:
"A True Warrior"